<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Servers>

       <ServerGroup Name="Resident Evil Mod (v1.1) - Spencer Mansion Incident" Logo="" Description="">

               <Server Name="Resident Evil Mod (v1.1) - Spencer Mansion Incident" Logo="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Frantic-Dan/Spencer-Mansion-Incident-v1-Mod-v5.0/main/Mods/ZZYSpencerMansion_Standalone/Config/backgrounds/ML-Imagedisplay.png">

                       <Description>
Have you ever wanted to play Resident Evil in first person? Well now you can!
STORY: Experience the 1998 Spencer Mansion Incident as Jill Valentine. Collect keys, solve puzzles, manage your limited resources and escape from the Survival Horror.

Setup:
1) Requires version *** v1.1 *** vanilla files to work.
2) It will always be night, so be sure to change the Zombie Night Speed to your liking. (Walk is recommended)
3) WARNING: Do NOT delete any of your saves until you have finished playing the mod entirely, or you'll have to load up a vanilla save to gain access to the new game window.
Or recreate the folder for the deleted save the game tries to access.

PLEASE NOTE: 
1) The Spencer Mansion Incident is a unique and challenging mod, and will test your combat and maneuverability skills.
2) Are your observation skills good enough to make it out alive?
3) Two-player is NOT supported anymore! (Custom code isn't compatible and bugs out, I'm sorry!)
4) Twitch Integration is NOT supported!!

KEY FEATURES:
1) Limited Inventory: You'll be restricted to the 10 slot toolbelt.
2) Doors are indestructible, however, zombies can open unlocked doors.
3) You cannot jump.
4) Zombies can revive into Crimson heads if not dispatched correctly!
5) Ink Ribbons for Manual Saving!
6) If you die, simply exit your game and reload your save (requires saving first).

FOR EXTRA IMMERSION:
1) Increase the volume of ambient sounds about 50%.
2) Set music to play 100% of the time.
3) Lighting is balanced for 50% brightness. There is a portable light source to be found.

Known Issue: DirectoryNotFoundException
For those who installed using the Mod Launcher, you'll likely get this error.
Could not find a part of the path
'C:\7D2D\v1\SpencerMansion_Incident-Resident_Evil\Spencer_Mansion_Incident-_Resident_Evil_Jill_Valentines_Story\Saves\YourPreviousMapYouPlayed\YourPreviousGameNameYouPlayed'.

You will need to navigate your PC directory to the 'Saves' folder, then create both of these new folders that the game is trying to access.
First folder inside the Saves folder, then open the newly created folder to create the second folder. The spelling needs to be exact.




                       </Description>

                       <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>

                       <SubscriptionLink>https://community.7daystodie.com/topic/27467-the-spencer-mansion-incident-resident-evil-v11/</SubscriptionLink>

                       <Version>v1.1 b4</Version>

                       <ReleaseNotes/>

                       <Downloads>

                       <Download>https://github.com/Frantic-Dan/Spencer-Mansion-Incident-v1-Mod-v5.0</Download>
					   

                 </Downloads>

						 <Discord>https://discord.gg/4A5MF8GHM5</Discord>
						 
						 <Donate>https://streamlabs.com/frantic_dan/tip</Donate>
						 
						 <Website>https://community.7daystodie.com/topic/27467-the-spencer-mansion-incident-resident-evil-v11/</Website>

               </Server>

       </ServerGroup>

</Servers>